ILGWU. Publications 5780 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU. Publications
1056-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780 PUBS
45.19 cubic feet
42.5 linear feet
Publications.
This collection contains publications created or collected by the ILGWU.
7461894
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
August 2011
EAD encoding:
Cheryl Beredo, August 2011
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was founded in New York City in 1900 by mostly Socialist immigrant workers who sought to unite the various crafts in the growing women's garment industry. The union soon reflected changes in the sector and rapidly organized thousands of unskilled and semi-skilled women, mostly Jewish and Italian young immigrants. Exemplifying the "new unionism," the ILGWU led two of the most widespread and best-known industrial strikes of the early Twentieth Century: the shirtwaist makers' strike of 1909 in New York City and the cloak makers' strike of 1910 in Chicago. The union also tried to adapt to the fragmented and unstable nature of the industry. It adopted the "protocol of peace," a system of industrial relations that attempted to ensure stability and limit strikes and production disruption by providing for an arbitration system to resolve disputes.
The ILGWU exemplified the European-style social unionism of its founding members. They pursued bread and butter issues but provided educational opportunities, benefits, and social programs to union members as well. In 1919, the ILGWU became the first American union to negotiate an unemployment compensation fund that was contributed to by its employers. The ILGWU also pioneered in the establishment of an extremely progressive health care program for its members which included not only regional Union Health Centers but also a resort for union workers, known as Unity House. The Union also had an imaginative and pioneering Education Department which not only trained workers in traditional union techniques, but provided courses in citizenship and the English language.
David Dubinsky, an immigrant from Belarus who came to the US in 1911, provided strong leadership that led to unprecedented growth in the union during his presidency from 1932 to 1966. He led the union through successful internal anti-communist struggles, built on the ascendancy of industrial unionism by encouraging the formation of the Committee for Industrial Organization, and helped the union become an important political force in New York City and state politics, and in the national Democratic Party and Liberal Party as well.
In the period following the Second World War, the union suffered a decline in membership as manufacturers avoided unionization and took advantage of less expensive labor by moving shops from the urban centers in the northeast to the south, and later abroad. The ethnic and racial character of the ILGWU also changed as European immigrants were supplanted by Asians, Latin Americans, African- Americans, and immigrants from the Caribbean.
In July 1995 the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) at a joint convention, forming UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees). At the time the new union had a membership of about 250,000 in the United States, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains publications created or collected by the ILGWU.
Conditions Governing Access
The ILGWU Records, except for publications and materials produced for publication, are restricted. Materials created prior to twenty years from the current date are open to researchers only with prior written permission from the Director of the Kheel Center; materials created during the past twenty-years are closed; the minutes of the General Executive Board are closed. For more information contact the Kheel Center.
General
"Permanent deposit."
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- History -- United States; Clothing workers -- United States -- History; Clothing industry -- United States -- History
7461894
- At Your Service, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  2 copies.
- At Your Service, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- At Your Service, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Luigi Antonini: His Influence on Italian-American Relations (Box 1, Folder 2)
- At Work, At Play, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  5 copies.
- Three Years: A Record of Achievement, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Eastern Out-of-Town Department Convention Report 1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Apparel Producer Magazine, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Apparel Manufacturing Industry, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The Apparel Manufacturing Industry, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- After a Life of Labor: A Pioneering Union's Program for Retirees, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- An American Adventure in Workers' Education, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The ABC of Parliamentary Law (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The ABC of Parliamentary Law, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The ABC of Parliamentary Law, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- …and the pursuit of happiness, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- The ABC of Trade Unionism (Box 1, Folder 12)
- An American Adventure in Workers' Education and The Workers' Education Bureau-An Arm of the Labor Movement, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- American Labor Faces the Future (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Blue Book of Chicago Fashion Sources (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Der Groyser Kampf Fun Di Klokmakher Fun 1910 Biz 1916 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Yiddish
- Where to Buy In the Cleveland Apparel Market (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Der Groyser Kundes (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Bundle Control (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Testimonial Dinner-Dance, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- The International Kibitzer, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- The Big Shot, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  10 copies.
- The Big Shot (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
- The Big Shot. Vol.II, No. A-1, 1940 (Box 1.1, Folder 1)
  6 copies.
- The Big Shot Vol. III, No.4-F (Box 1.1, Folder 2)
- Delegates Guide: Big Shot Edition, 1974 (Box 1.1, Folder 3)
- The "Little" Big Shot Vol.II, No.B-4 (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
  3 copies.
- The Big Shot Vol. III, No.4-F (Box 1.1, Folder 4)
- Cartoons, 1947-1950 (Box 1.1, Folder 5)
  5 copies
- Here's How to Sell What We Sew (Box 1.1, Folder 6)
- Our Rights and Responsibilities (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Union (Box 2, Folder 2)
- La Union (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Spanish
- Why Workers Must Vote (Box 2, Folder 4)
- To My Co-Workers and Friends, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- The CIO, Labor's New Challenge (Box 2, Folder 6)
- The CIO at the Convention of the ILGWU, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Yiddish titles (Box 2, Folder 8)
- The Case Against David Dubinsky, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- The Church and Unionism, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Cartoons from the 1950's in the ILGWU Justice, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  4 copies.
- Celebrating the Gold and Silver Jubilee of the Chicago ILGWU (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Census, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1961, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1962, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1963, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1964, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1965, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1966, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1967, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1968, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1969, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1970, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1971, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1977, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1979, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Census Report 1981, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Members of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- In the Matter of The Cleveland Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Dress Industry, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Cleveland and its Cloakmakers (Box 3, Folder 6)
- A Cloakmaker Looks at Stolberg's "Tailor's Progress", 1944 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Vi Azoy Stolberes Bukh "Teylors Progres" Zet Oysindi Oyen Fur A Klokmaker (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Guarantee of Employment Control Book (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Klokmakher Benshmin Sehlesinker (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Yiddish. 5 copies.
- Code of Fair Competition for the Coat and Suit Industry, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Code of Fair Competition for the Coat and Suit Industry, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Code of Fair Competition for the Cotton Garment Industry, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Amendment to the Code of Fair Competition for the Cotton Garment Industry, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Code of Fair Competition, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Code of Fair Competition for the Dress Manufacturing Industry, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Code of Fair Competition for the Dress Manufacturing Industry (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Amendment to Code of Fair Competition for the Dress Manufacturing Industry, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Objections of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Draft of Proposed Amended Code Submitted by the ILGWU (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Conciliation, Arbitration and Sanitation in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Industry, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  2 copies
- Conditions in the Cloak and Suit Industry in the City of New York, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Communists in Control (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Como Entenderse Mejor (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Spanish. 4 copies.
- Der Konstruktiver Yumyonizm (Box 4, Folder 5)
- The Consumers' Protection Label (Box 4, Folder 6)
- The Contractor's Reply to the Union and Jobbers' Demands on Reorganization and Efficiency for the Dress Manufacturing Industry, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- The International Kibitzer Vol. X, No.Y, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Konvenshon Moskito (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Yiddish. 2 copies.
- Konvenshon Gergele (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Yiddish. 3 copies.
- Konvenshon Kolokotke (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Yiddish. 4 copies.
- Konvenshon Kanarik, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  English and Yiddish. 40th Convention. 6 copies.
- The Cloak Maker's Strike, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Council of Conciliation, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Der Krizis Un "Dio Kloukmakhfr" (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Yiddish.
- Der Krizis Un Di Nodl-Fakhn (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Local 10 Cutters' Almanac, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Going Forward, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Cutters Defense League Annual Dance Souvenir Journal, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Harper's Magazine, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- The Depression and After in the Women's Garment Industry, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Development of the Dress Industry (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A Democratic Foreign Policy for the United States, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Double Texture: A Profile of David Gingold, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- The Dress Industry, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- 15th Anniversary Banquet of Dress Pressers JNWA, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Tenth Anniversary Dress Pressers Branch Workmen's Circle, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Twentieth Anniversary Dress Pressers Branch 761-E (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Proposal for Suggested Changes in the Agreement between Dress and Waist Manufacturers' and the ILGWU and its Locals, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Democracy and the Nature of Man (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Dresses. The Impact of Fashion on a Business, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- The Emancipator Vol.2, No.3, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Time Magazine Vol. LIV, No. 9 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- The New Leader, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Labor History Vol. 9 Supplement, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- The "Dubinsky Issue" in the 1936 Campaign (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Earnings in the Women's and Children's Apparel Industry in the Spring of 1939, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Report to the 29th Convention ILGWU, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Report to the 28th Convention-ILGWU (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Report to the 26th Convention-ILGWU, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Report to the 25th Convention-ILGWU, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Three Years- A Record of Achievement 1934-1937; Report to the 23rd Convention-ILGWU (Box 6, Folder 4)
- The Eastern Out-of-Town Department: Its Structure and Functioning, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- The End of the Communist Adventure in the Garment Unions (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Employed Women Under NRA Codes- Bulletin No.130, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Equal Opportunity Union Made (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Der Sof Fun Der Komunistisher Avanture Un Der Interneshonal Leydis Garment Yoyarers Yunyon (Box 6, Folder 9)
- The Eye Route: Visual Aids for Workers' Education (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Fifty Years of Struggle: The History of the ILGWU in Cincinnati (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Facts for Eastern Region ILGWU Members, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- What Everybody Should Know about the Fair Labor Standards Act (1938 Wage and Hour Law) (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Fifty Years of Fashion, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- A Fighting Program for the Dressmakers, 1937 (Box 6.1, Folder 1)
- The Fight's Just Begun: Fifty Years with Local 66, 1963 (Box 6.1, Folder 2)
- Manufacturers' Bulletin for Fire Protection in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt and the Dress and Waist Industries, 1915 (Box 6.1, Folder 3)
- Findings and Recommendations of the Council of Conciliation, 1915 (Box 6.1, Folder 4)
- Five Years' Work and Progress of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt and Dress and Waist Industries, 1910 (Box 6.1, Folder 5)
- Formative Years of the Jewish Labor Movement in the United States, 1945 (Box 6.1, Folder 6)
- Di Yo-Shtundige Arbeyts-Vod (Box 6.1, Folder 7)
- Friendly Visiting to the Aged in Institutions (Box 6.1, Folder 8)
- From the Heart of the ILGWU Membership (Box 6.1, Folder 9)
- The Future of the New York Apparel Industry 1952-1970 (preliminary), 1953 (Box 6.1, Folder 10)
- Gerekhtigkayt (Box 6.1, Folder 11)
- Life Magazine, Garment Workers at Play, 1938 (Box 6.1, Folder 12)
- Gerekhtigkayt (Box 6.1, Folder 13)
- Gerekhtigkayt (Box 6.1, Folder 14)
- Samuel Gompers' Credo (Box 6.1, Folder 15)
- Govern Altoeld (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Grades and Body Prices, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Growing Up: 21 Years of Education with the ILGWU, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Handbook (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Handbook for Members (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Handbook of Trade Union Methods, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- The Hart Schaffner and Marx Labor Agreement: Industrial Law in the Garment Industry, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Health Services, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Health and Welfare in the Ladies' Garment Industry; Health and Welfare Funds and History in the Making (Box 8, Folder 5)
- History of the Sewing Machine (Box 8, Folder 6)
- The Holeproof Union Story (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Re the Hourwich Affair: A Statement from the General Executive Board of the ILGWU (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Hometown Union: The Story of the ILGWU in Fall River and Vicinity (Box 8, Folder 9)
- How to Conduct a Union Meeting, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- How to Conduct a Union Meeting, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- How to Start Classes: Methods and Materials in Workers' Education Activities for Trade Unions, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Benefits: What You Should Know About Them (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Health, Vacation and Welfare Fund: By-Laws in Brief (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Benefits, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Hospital Surgical-Medical and Major Medical Benefits, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Five Years' Experience with a New Mobile Health Survey Program (Box 8, Folder 17)
- By-Laws Vacation Fund (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Constitution and By-Laws of Sick Benefit Fund and Tuberculosis Benefit Fund, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Health and Welfare Plan for Designers and Dependents, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Constitution and By-Laws (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Schedule of Benefits, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Rules and Regulations of the Health and Welfare Fund of Dress Joint Board (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Rules and Regulations: Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry in the New York Metropolitan Area (Box 8, Folder 24)
- The Health and Welfare Fund (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Union Health Center Annual Report 1943 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Health Plan (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Local 60 Health Plan: Dress and Waist Pressers' Union (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Rules and Regulations: Retirement Fund of Snow Suit, Skiwear, Leggings and Infants' Novelty Wear Industry (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Report for the Year 1937 on the Sick Benefit Plan of the Children's Dress, Infants' Wear, Housedress and Bathrobe Makers' Union, Local 91 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Rules and Regulations of the Vacation and Health Benefit Fund (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Su Centro de Salud de la Union y Como Hacer Uso de El: Toda la Informacion que usted necesita (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Spanish.
- Opening the Door to Health (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Ceremonies and Inspection of Facilities Marking Completion of Expansion Program (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Report of the Director for 1936, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- The Union Health Center Committee of the ILGWU (Box 9, Folder 11)
- L.A. Union Health Center Organization and Operation (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Union Health Center ILGWU, Philadelphia and Vicinity, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Rules and Regulations of the Health and Vacation Fund of Cloak Joint Board (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Security on the March: Health and Welfare Services, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Your Retirement Fund: How it Works, Operates and How You Benefit (Box 9, Folder 16)
- The Union Health Center of the ILGWU: Questions and Answers, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Here's to Your Health: Health, Retirement, Death Benefits for Union Members (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Report of Survey of The Union Health Center and Hospital Benefit Program, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Rules and Regulations of the Retirement Fund, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Death Benefit Fund: Rules and Regulations (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Report: Death Benefit Fund, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Report: Death Benefit Fund, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Report: Death Benefit Fund, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Death Benefit Fund, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Death Benefit Fund of the ILGWU, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Death Benefit Fund of the ILGWU, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Death Benefit Fund of the ILGWU, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Death Benefit Fund of the ILGWU, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Rules and Regulations of the Retirement Fund of the Dress Industry of New York, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Rules and Regulations of the Health and Welfare Fund, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Rules and Regulations of the Retirement Fund, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Information and Instructions for Local Union Office Managers on Procedures Relating to the ILGWU Death Benefit Fund (Box 9, Folder 30)
- To Your Health! (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Program of the Health and Welfare Fund (Box 9, Folder 32)
- American Opinion Vol.VI, No.5, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Rules and Regulations of the Health and Welfare Fund (Box 9, Folder 34)
- For the Record…, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Health and Welfare Benefit Program (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Report of the Investigating Committee Submitted to the Retirement Board of the Coat and Suit Industry of New York (Box 10, Folder 2)
- The Thread of Life (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Important Rules and Regulations Relief Fund and Wage Schedule (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Report on the Medical Administration of Sick Benefits (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Report of the Union Health Center to the 23rd Convention of the ILGWU (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Health and Welfare Benefits Program (Box 10, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Union Health Center Local 178 1934-1944 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Rules and Regulations: Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry in the New York Metropolitan Area (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Major Medical Program (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Sick Benefit Fund: Rules and regulations (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Sick Benefit Fund: Rules and Regulations (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Report on the Medical Administration of Sick Benefits (Box 10, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Staff Retirement Fund Summary and Plan (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Better Medical Care That You Can Afford (Box 10, Folder 15)
- 1927-1928 Calendar. Union Health Center. (Box 10, Folder 16)
- What You Must Know About The Health Fund (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Constitution of the Sick Benefit Fund, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Financial Report of the Health, Welfare and Retirement Funds, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Financial Report of the Health, Welfare and Retirement Funds, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Financial Report of the Health, Welfare and Retirement Funds, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Financial Report of the Health, Welfare, Retirement and Supplementary Unemployment-Severance Funds, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Physician Services Received by Dress Joint Board Members, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Rules and Regulations of the Coat and Suit Designers' Health and Welfare Fund, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Rules and Regulations: Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry of Philadelphia, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Advisory Opinion Submitted to the Investment Committee of the Retirement Board of the Coat and Suit Industry of New York, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Constitution of the Sick Benefit Fund, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Konstitushon Fun Sik Benefit Fond Department Kouk Mayker Yunion (Box 11, Folder 3)
- All About Your Benefits (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Fondo de Beneficios Por Fallecimiento de la ILGWU Reglas y Regulaciones, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Annual Report 1948 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- St. Louis Post-Dispatch Pictures, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Rules and Regulations of the Health Fund, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Report on the Labor Situation in the Coat and Suit Industry, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Montreal Fashion Industry Health Services Plan, Inc., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Montreal Cloak Industry Severance Pay Fund, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Montreal Cloak Industry Tie- In Agreement, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Montreal Cloak Industry Health Fund, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- The Fashion Accessories Industry Health Fund, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Dress Severance Pay Fund, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Embroidery Severance Pay Fund, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Dress Industry Health Fund Contracts (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Welfare Funds Tie-In Agreement, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Industrial Court of the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Industry of New York City, 1914 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- "I Make Dresses", 1935 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- The Electrical Workers' Journal, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and Workers' Education, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Monthly Labor Review Vol.73 No.5, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Annual Journal ILGWU, 1904 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Introducing Your Union, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Introduction to Labor Problems, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- "I Was There" Israel- 1949 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- In Defense of "Contractor Limitation" and "Jobbers' Responsibility" (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Industrial Planning Through Collective Bargaining, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 12)